





TABREZ ALAM

GRAPHIC DESIGNER (Multimedia Expert)

About Me

Designer Specialist with over 2 and a half + years of experience in Multimedia Designing and Multimedia Artist. Expert with a wide variety of designing and in the Graphic Designing Training Field.

Language - Hindi, English

Contact



PHONE

+91-882-267-9890

Gmail



tabrezsheikh162@gmail.com



ADDRESS

Mahewa Naini, Allahabad Uttar Pradesh - 211007

SKILLS

CORELDRAW
ILLUSTRATOR







EDUCATION

- On 10th From Divyabha Convent Got 73.3% (2016)
 - 12th From Divyabha Convent Got 58.9% (2018)
- B.sc Graduated (2019-21)
- Graphics Design From NexGen (Next Generation Computer Education)
- Learning Video Editing / VFX & 3D From Youtube and Udemy.

EXPERIENCE

- 6 Months Of Internship From NexGen Institute as Graphic Designer (2019)
 - 6 Month Of Assistant Trainer in NexGen Institute. (2019-20)
- Working as a Senior Designer in coreldrawdesign.com (2019-Present)
- Working in Empretus Technology (Mother Company of coreldrawdesign.com)2019-Present
- Working as a Senior Graphic Designer at Major Kalshi Classes (2021-2022)

Interest

Watching Animated Movies, Playing Games & Travelling.